Igor Doslov

PROGRAMMER

Sydney, NSW

igordoslov.dev@gmail.com

☐ https://igordoslov.github.io

in Igor Doslov

PROFILE

I'm a programmer who specialises in gameplay programming. I'm passionate about programming because it allows me to create and be part of something I care about - games. I enjoy problem-solving and working as a team. My goals is to work on fun games that I am passionate about while learning from others in the gaming industry.

SKILLS

Technologies

- Unity
- Visual Studio
- C#
- C++

Source Control

- Git
- Branching
- Merging

Collaboration

- Sprints
- Standups
- Agile workflow

WORK EXPERIENCE

GAME PROGRAMMER

July 2021 - Nov 2021

4th Dimension - Student Project: Wasteland Wanderer

- Collaborated with a team of seven from Proof of Concept to Gold.
- Identifying and solving bugs.
- · Worked within the Unity engine.
- Used source control to manage code with other team members.

GAME PROGRAMMER

Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

Pyrite - Student Project: Earl the Teabag

- Collaborated with a team of five from Proof of Concept to Gold.
- Worked to a client brief.
- Participated in daily stand up meetings while working to a schedule.
- · Adhered to coding standards.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Feb 2021 - Dec 2021

Advanced Diploma of Professional Game Development, Specialising in Programming

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Diploma of Digital and Interactive Games, Specialising in Programming

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Feb 2012 - Dec 2015

Bachelor of Digital Media

UNSW